// Questions - The Tortured Poets Department

export const theTorturedPoetsDepartmentQuestions = [
    {
    "question": "All my mornings are Mondays stuck in an endless February",
    "answers": ["Fornight", "Florida!!!", "loml", "The Alchemy"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "I scratch your head, you fall asleep",
    "answers": ["So Long, London", "Down Bad", "Clara Bow", "The Tortured Poets Department"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "How dare you think it's romantic leaving me safe and stranded",
    "answers": ["Guilty as Sin", "The Black Dog", "Down Bad", "The Albatross"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "I didn't opt in to be your odd man out",
    "answers": ["The Prophecy", "So Long, London", "How Did it End?", "Cassandra"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Growing up precocious sometimes means not growing up at all",
    "answers": ["loml", "The Bolter", "Clara Bow", "But Daddy I Love Him"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Handcuffed to the spell I was under",
    "answers": ["Fresh Out the Slammer", "The Alchemy", "The Black Dog", "Florida!!!"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "All my girls got their lace and their crimes",
    "answers": ["loml", "The Tortured Poets Department", "Florida!!!", "Guilty as Sin"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Building up like waves, crashing over my grave",
    "answers": ["The Black Dog", "Guilty as Sin", "imgonnagetyouback", "The Albatross"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "When your impressionist paintings of heaven turned out to be fakes",
    "answers": ["How Did it End?", "So High School", "I Hate it Here", "loml"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Cause the sign on your heart said it's still reserved for me",
    "answers": ["The Alchemy", "Clara Bow", "Thank You Aimee", "Cassandra"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "The crown is stained but you're the real queen",
    "answers": ["Fortnight", "But Daddy I Love Him", "Clara Bow", "Down Bad"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Were you making fun of me with some esoteric joke?",
    "answers": ["I Hate it Here", "The Black Dog", "So High School", "Robin"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Flip the script and leave you like a dumb house party ",
    "answers": ["Peter", "loml", "Guilty as Sin", "imgonnagetyouback"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Wise men once read fake news",
    "answers": ["The Albatross", "I Hate it Here", "Cassandra", "Clara Bow"],
    "correct": 0 
    },

    {
    "question": "My beloved ghost and me, sitting in a tree",
    "answers": ["Thank You Aimee", "I Look in People's Windows", "How Did it End?", "Peter"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "You know how to ball, I know Aristotle",
    "answers": ["The Prophecy", "So High School", "The Alchemy", "The Bolter"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Nostalgia is a mind's trick",
    "answers": ["The Manuscript", "Robin", "The Black Dog", "I Hate it Here"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "I built a legacy that you can't undo",
    "answers": ["The Bolter", "Thank You Aimee", "The Albatross", "imgonnagetyouback"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Transfixed by rose golden glows",
    "answers": ["The Prophecy", "I Look in People's Windows", "Florida!!!", "So Long, London"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "But I howl like a wolf at the moon",
    "answers": ["The Prophecy", "How Did it End?", "The Manuscript", "Cassandra"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "When the truth comes out, it's quiet ",
    "answers": ["So High School", "Fortnight", "The Tortured Poets Department", "Cassandra"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "The goddess of timing once found us beguiling",
    "answers": ["imgonnagetyouback", "Peter", "loml", "Guilty as Sin"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "It feels like the time she fell through the ice",
    "answers": ["The Bolter", "So High School", "Fresh Out the Slammer", "But Daddy I Love Him"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "You got the dragonflies above your bed ",
    "answers": ["Peter", "Cassandra", "Robin", "Clara Bow"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "And at last she knew what the agony had been for",
    "answers": ["The Prophecy", "Thank You Aimee", "loml", "The Manuscript"],
    "correct": 3
    },
];